Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education In Asia Records, Addendum A
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Related Organizations and Publications--Addendum, Series VI
  - Related Organizations
    - COCHEA: Colleges-Philippines: Wilson, Frank T., Report: Survey of Church Related Schools, 1959 Apr (Box 259, Folder 3585)
    - COCHEA:Colleges-Philippines: Central Philippine University, 1956, 1958 (Box 259, Folder 3586)
    - COCHEA:Colleges-Philippines: Harris Memorial School, 1958 (Box 259, Folder 3586)
    - COCHEA:Colleges-Philippines: Southern Christian College, 1958 (Box 259, Folder 3586)
    - COCHEA:Colleges-Philippines: Union Theological Seminary, 1952-1959, n.d. (Box 259, Folder 3587)
    - COCHEA: Colleges -Singapore: Trinity College, 1953 (Box 259, Folder 3588)
    - Inter-Institutional Consortium (Philippines) (Box 259, Folder 3588)
    - Committee of Science Dept. Heads-- Teaching Materials, 1977 (Box 260, Folder 3589)
    - National Board of Christian Higher Education in India (See also: All-India Association for Christian Higher): Minutes, Reports, 1968-1971, n.d. (Box 260, Folder 3590-3591)
    - National Board of Christian Higher Education in India: Journal of Christian Colleges in India, 1967-1970 (Box 260, Folder 3592)
    - National Board of Christian Higher Education in India: Newsletter, 1969-1970 (Box 260, Folder 3593)
    - National Board of Christian Higher Education in India: Report of Second Triennial National Conference, 1969/ 1970 (Box 260, Folder 3594)
    - Smith-Ginling: Ginling Committee of Smith College: Secretary's Notebook, 1924-1933 (Box 279, Folder 3924)
    - Smith-Ginling: Alumnae Gifts to Ginling, 1928-1952 (Box 279, Folder 3925-3927)
    - Smith-Ginling: Correspondence, 1951-1956 (Box 279, Folder 3928)
    - Smith-Ginling: Miscellaneous, 1940-1954, n.d. (Box 279, Folder 3929)
    - Smith-Ginling: Smith Clubs: letters to club presidents ant Ginling representatives, 1936-1954 (Box 279, Folder 3930-3931)
    - Smith-Ginling: Smith Clubs: Member Lists, 1937-1948 (Box 279, Folder 3932)
    - Smith-Ginling: Spring Appeal, 1949 (Box 279, Folder 3933)
    - Wellesley-Yenching: Fund-raising Appeals, 1939-1952 (Box 280, Folder 3934-3935)
    - Wellesley-Yenching: Giving Reports, 1940-1947 (Box 280, Folder 3936)
    - Wellesley-Yenching: Chung Chi Teaching Representative, 1959-1968 (Box 280, Folder 3937-3938)
    - Wellesley-Yenching: Moore, Elisabeth Luce (Mrs. Maurice T.), 1941-1953 (Box 280, Folder 3939)
    - Wellesley-Yenching Committee: Correspondence, Reports, 1940-1954 (Box 280, Folder 3940)
  - Princeton-in-Asia (formerly known as Princeton- in-Peking and Princeton-Yenching)
    - Administrative
      - Board of Trustees, 1929-1933 (Box 261, Folder 3595-3597)
      - Executive Committee, 1923-1930 (Box 261, Folder 3598-3606)
      - Finance Committee, 1923-1924 (Box 261, Folder 3607)
      - Finance and Executive Committees, 1931-1933 (Box 261, Folder 3608-3610)
      - Finance and Executive Committees, 1934-1948 (Box 262, Folder 3611-3616)
      - International Committee, 1933-1934 (Box 262, Folder 3617)
      - Members Meeting, 1930-1953 (Box 262, Folder 3618-3621)
      - Sub-Committees of National Council of Y.M.C.A. and Princeton-in-Peking Minutes of Yenching Univ. Committees:, 1926-1927 (Box 262, Folder 3622)
      - Auditing Committee, 1929 Jun (Box 262, Folder 3623)
      - Board of Managers, 1928-1931 (Box 262, Folder 3624-3627)
      - Board of Trustees, 1927-1930 (Box 262, Folder 3628-3632)
      - Board of Trustees, 1930-1932 (Box 263, Folder 3633-3637)
      - Board of Trustees, Executive Committee, 1928-1932 (Box 263, Folder 3638-3640)
      - Budget Committee, 1929-1932 (Box 263, Folder 3641-3644)
      - Campaign Committee, 1928 (Box 263, Folder 3645)
      - Committee of Yenching College for Women, 1928-1932 (Box 263, Folder 3646-3650)
      - Committee on McBrier Foundation, 1931-1932 (Box 263, Folder 3651-3652)
      - Committee on Promotion, 1932 (Box 263, Folder 3653)
      - Committee on Salary and Pensions, 1930 (Box 263, Folder 3654)
      - Constitution and By-Laws, 1928 (Box 263, Folder 3655)
      - Finance Committee, 1927-1928 (Box 263, Folder 3656-3658)
      - Finance Committee, 1929-1932 (Box 264, Folder 3659-3672)
      - Grounds and Buildings Committee, 1928 (Box 264, Folder 3673)
      - Grounds and Buildings Committee, 1929 (Box 264, Folder 3674)
      - Reorganization Committee, 1928 (Box 264, Folder 3675)
      - Special Promotional Committee, Executive Committee, 1931 (Box 264, Folder 3676)
    - Consolidated General File
      - All consolidated general file boxes have been transferred to Princeton-in-Asia office in Princeton, NJ
      - Photographs (See Series V: Audio-Visual Materials, Princeton-in-Asia)
  - Related Publications
    - Concerning Education
      - "The Significance for Religious Education of Modern Educational Trends in China," by Chen Ching-Szu, 1940 (Box 281, Folder 3941)
      - Report of Survey Evaluation of Twenty Church-Related Schools in Thailand, 1964 (Box 281, Folder 3942)
      - Korean Universities and Colleges, ed. by Rudolf Klimes, 1967 (Box 281, Folder 3943)
      - "The Role of Universities in the Developing Philippines," by E. Castro Resposo, 1971 (Box 281, Folder 3944)
      - "The Role of Private Higher Education in the Philippines" - Final Report, Private Higher Education Survey, 1975 (Box 281, Folder 3945)
      - "Profiles of Philippine Univeraities and Colleges" - Philippine-American Educational Foundation, 1975 (Box 281, Folder 3946)
      - "The Catholic Universities of Indonesia", 1980 (Box 282, Folder 3947)
    - Conference Publications
      - Second UBCHEA Conference of Administrators, International Christian University, Japan, 1957 (Box 282, Folder 3948)
      - Third UBCHEA Conference of Christian University Presidents, Silliman University, The Philippines, 1958 (Box 282, Folder 3949)
      - International Conference on University Planning and Development, The Seoul National University, Korea, 1971 (Box 282, Folder 3950)
      - National Consultation workshop on Education, St. Andrew's Theological Seminary, The Philippines, 1972 (Box 282, Folder 3951)
      - First Asian Conference Workshop in Guidance and Counseling, Manila, 1976 (Box 282, Folder 3952)
      - Asian Water Pollution Conference, Silliman Univeraity, The Philippines, 1977 (Box 283, Folder 3953)
      - Third Asian Conference Workshop in Guidance and Counseling, Salatiga, Indonesia, 1980 (Box 283, Folder 3954)
      - Workshop on Curriculum and Syllabus Evaluation and Design, Indonesia, 1981 (Box 283, Folder 3955)